<resources>
    <string name="app_name">medgift</string>
    <string name="welcomeTitle">Welcome to MedGift</string>
    <string name="application_logo">Application Logo</string>
    <string name="lblEmail">Email</string>
    <string name="lblPassword">Password</string>
    <string name="lblLoginBtn">Login</string>
    <string name="lblSignup">Sign up</string>
    <string name="txtNoAccount">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="registerTitle">Hello! Register to get started</string>
    <string name="lblFullname">Full Name</string>
    <string name="lblConfirmPassword">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="txtHasAccount">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="lblLogin">Login</string>
    <string name="rdlblGifter">I am a Healthcare Service Gifter</string>
    <string name="rdlblProvider">I am a Healthcare Service Provider</string>
    <string name="lblRegisterBtn">Register</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="more_health_tips"><![CDATA[More Health Tips >]]></string>
    <string name="health_tips">Health Tips</string>
    <string name="for_you">For You</string>
    <string name="group_gifts">Group Gifts</string>
    <string name="gift_care">Gift Care</string>
    <string name="service_categories">Service Categories</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="available_services">Available Services</string>
    <string name="recipients">Recipients</string>
    <string name="gifts">Gifts</string>
    <string name="sample_title">Title</string>
    <string name="sample_provider">Provider</string>
    <string name="sample_location">Location</string>
    <string name="sample_description">Description</string>
    <string name="sample_rating_count">1,944</string>
    <string name="sample_price">$ xxx.xx</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="tip_description">The best defense against dehydration is prevention. Follow these six tips to stay safe and healthy, especially when temperatures — or your activity levels — increase:

1. Don’t wait till you’re thirsty to drink
By the time you feel thirsty, you’re already slightly dehydrated. Sip water steadily throughout the day and drink more fluids than usual when the weather is hot, especially if you’re active.



If you need a reminder to stay hydrated, carry a reusable water bottle with you and set a timer on your phone to notify you to drink water throughout the day.

2. Flavor your water
If plain water tastes boring to you, you can add flavor with fresh fruits or a splash of fruit juice. You can also consume clear broths, ice pops or sports drinks (especially if you’re doing intense exercise). Just make sure to limit caffeine and alcohol.

3. Eat water-rich fruits and vegetables.
Certain fruits and vegetables are high in water content and nutrients. Watermelon, strawberries, cantaloupe, peaches and pineapples are fruits with high-water content. Water-rich vegetables include cucumbers, leafy greens, radishes, celery, zucchini and tomatoes.

4. Stay inside when it gets too hot
Avoid sun exposure, especially between 10 am and 2 pm, when the rays are strongest. Instead, plan outdoor activities in the early morning or evening.



Consider exercising indoors with air conditioning instead of exercising outside in scorching hot weather. If you usually hike or run outside, try swimming instead.



Stay indoors to avoid the heat, even if you’re not working out. If you don’t have air conditioning at home, try a shopping center, movie theater or public library.

5. Dress for the weather
Wear light, loose-fitting clothing that lets your skin breathe. Dark colors absorb heat, so stick with lighter shades. Wear a wide-brimmed hat in the sun to keep your head cool and use plenty of sunscreen to avoid sunburn, which can increase your skin temperature and make it harder to stay cool.

6. Be aware of the signs of dehydration
Dehydration is common and can affect anyone, but some people are more at risk, especially children and older adults.



Children are at higher risk of dehydration because they have a higher percentage of water in their bodies, which decreases with age. Children also may not always realize they are thirsty and may forget to drink enough water.



Older adults are at higher risk of dehydration due to age-related health problems and decreased thirst sensation.



“Older people may forget to drink water or not recognize their thirst,” says Dr. Ly. “They might also neglect to prevent dehydration the same way a younger person would. Be cognizant about that if you have a parent or older person around.”



Keep an eye out for any of these signs of dehydration:



Darker-than-usual urine
Not urinating despite steadily drinking water
Muscle cramps
Bad breath
Fatigue
Fever or chills
Craving sweets
Dry mouth/skin
Fast heartbeat
Irritability
Confusion
Drowsiness </string>
    <string name="tip_posting_date">14-10-2024</string>
</resources>